Finding Aid for the Edward Emerson Barnard Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Edward Emerson Barnard Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0031
19.32 linear feet
- Contents of Barnard Addition, 2010
  - Barnard’s publications before, 1907 (Box A, Folder 1)
  - Barnard’s publications in, 1907 (Box A, Folder 2)
  - Barnard’s publications from, 1908-1913 (Box A, Folder 3)
  - Barnard’s publications from, 1914-1922 (Box A, Folder 4)
  - Barnard’s Trigonometry Journal (Box A, Folder 5)
  - Two of Barnard’s Journals (Box A, Folder 6)
  - Two of Barnard’s Notebooks (Box A, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript for a booklet by Professor Frost (Box A, Folder 8)
  - Copy of Manuscript for a booklet by Professor Frost (Box A, Folder 9)
  - Photos of Barnard (Box B, Folder 1)
  - Photos of Barnard’s Watch (Box B, Folder 2)
  - Materials Related to Barnard’s Watch (Box B, Folder 3)
  - Barnard Personal Photos (Box B, Folder 4)
  - Photos from Glass Plates (Box B, Folder 5)
  - Mounted Photos and Clippings (Box B, Folder 6)
  - Photos from TN Road of Science, 1877 (Box B, Folder 7)
  - Photos of Moon from Lick Observatory (Box B, Folder 8)
  - Materials from Lick Observatory and Earthquake of, 1981 (Box B, Folder 9)
  - Original Records of Comet, 1886 (Box B, Folder 10)
  - Barnard’s Notes from, 1887 (Box B, Folder 11)
  - Barnard Astronom2y Material- Piece of Metal (Box B, Folder 12)
  - Barnard Astronomy Observations (photos or illustrations?) (Box B, Folder 13)
  - Barnard Astronomical Illustrations (Box B, Folder 14)
  - Letters to Barnard (Box B, Folder 15)
  - Notes by Barnard (Box B, Folder 16)
  - Publications about Barnard (Box B, Folder 17)
  - Letters from Barnard (Box B, Folder 18)
  - Materials Related to Barnard (Box B, Folder 19)
  - Barnard-Related Publications (Box B, Folder 20)
    - Photocopy of September 1893 Harper’s New Monthly magazine article on E.E. Barnard "Ad Astra” brochure with bio of Barnard with photos
    - "Mellish and Barnard – They Did See Martian Craters!” – 1975 astronomy publication